mysearchresults.com 2015-12-31

# Search Results — Privacy Policy

This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") for mysearchresults.com and/or other web domains owned and operated by Search Results, LLC. ("Website") that applies to your use of the Website and covers how Search Results, LLC. ("Search Results" "we," "us," or "our") treats information that it collects and receives about you via the Website, including the personal information we collect through the various features, programs, services, and software that we provide to you. Some of these offerings are provided by third parties who may provide you with additional information and choices about your privacy. If you choose to take advantage of these offerings, you should read the privacy policies of such third parties.

Please take a moment to review the terms of this Privacy Policy. By using the Website, you agree to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website. Please note that certain features or services discussed in this Privacy Policy may have separate privacy practices.

### Collection, Use and Disclosure of General Statistical Information and Automatically Collected Information

When you visit our web site we gather certain general information, such as frequency of downloads, number of hits on our web site, and usage statistics with respect to our software products. This information is referred to throughout this policy as "General Statistical Information". We use and store this data only on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us to determine how and the extent to which certain parts of our web site and software are used. The stored General Statistical Information does not contain any Personal Identifying Information about you or any of our other users.

When you open an HTML email message from us or install a third party application offered by us during installation of recommended software, we automatically record certain data using technology, including cookies (defined below) and IP addresses. Such data include the email message you opened and the third party application you installed. This information is referred to throughout this policy as "Automatically Collected Information." We store this data on an individual basis but it is used only in summary form. This data helps us evaluate the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. The stored Automatically Collected Information does not contain any Personal Identifying Information about you or any of our users.

### Personal Information We Collect

We may collect personal information at various times when you use our Services. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. Your participation is voluntary and you have the choice not to disclose any information that we request.

_Installation_ – During installation, we will present you with Offers. You may choose not to accept our Offers. Your participation is voluntary, you are not required to disclose to our Partners any information they request. However, if you provide your Personally Identifiable Information in response to any Offer, we will share it with our Partners so they can provide you with the Offers in which you have expressed interest.

_Contacts/IP Information_ – If you voluntarily submit information or contact us (e.g. password request, technical support), we may keep a record of this communication. We do not merge this information with your Personally Identifiable Information.

_Contact Us_ – We collect your name and email address on the Sites' "Contact us" forms. We use this information for the sole purpose of responding to your inquiry.

_Customer Support_ – If you use the customer support section on the Sites we will collect your email address, topic and any addition information you provide us. We use this information for the sole purpose of responding to your inquiry.

_Affiliate Sign Up_ – If you choose to sign up as an affiliate we will collect your name, company name, URL, mailing address, phone number and email address. Once we receive your application you will receive an email acknowledgement and instructions on how to pay to become an affiliate. We will not use your email address for any other purpose.

### Aggregate Information We Collect

When you use our Services, we may collect tracking information such as your IP address, browser type, the type of operating system you use, details about your computer hardware, the applications you have installed on your PC, the domain name of your Internet service provider, and pages you visited on our Sites. None of the information identifies you personally and we do not link aggregate information to Personally Identifiable Information.

_Cookies_ – A cookie is a small text file sent to your browser. Cookies are stored on your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. We and our Partners use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once you close your browser, the cookie will terminate. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's help file.

We use cookies to: 1) Remind us of who you are and to access your account information (stored on our computers). We also use cookies to store your zip code and other information you have submitted for other services, such as displaying your local weather; 2) Record your Blog URL and Username on your local computer to allow us to remember you on your next visit; 3) Estimate our audience size. Each browser accessing our Services is given a unique cookie which is then used to determine the extent of repeat usage, usage by registered users and unregistered users, and to help target advertisements based on user interests; 4) Allows our Partners to track visits to their sites and stores. This information collected by cookies is sometimes called "clickstream" or "click trail" and may also describe which pages you have seen; 5) Measure certain traffic patterns, for example which of our Sites you have visited. We use this information to understand our users' habits so that we can make each new experience on a Site a better one. We may also use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you will see. We do not store Personally Identifiable Information in our cookies and we do not tie the information in our cookies to our customers' Personally Identifiable Information.

Some of the Partner Offers on our Services may also use cookies. We have no control over our partners' privacy policies. We also have no control over their cookies, the information collected and its use.

_Web beacons or Pixels_ – We and our Partners employ a software technology that helps us better manage content on our site. Web beacons or Pixels are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. They track your online Web movement. We embed Pixels invisibly on Web pages. They are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by Pixels to our customers' Personally Identifiable Information. Some of the Partner Offers may also use Pixels. We have no control over our partners' Pixels. We also have no control over how they use information collected.

### Disclosure of Personal Identifying Information

Partners may sponsor Offers or we may co-sponsor an Offer with a Partner through the software. You should always assume data collected when you fill-in an Offer will be shared with a Partner. If an Offer requires you to leave our websites, you should know that our Partners may collect Personally Identifiable Information about you. We do not control these Partner sites. This Privacy Policy does not cover our partners' websites and information practices. Once you have voluntarily submitted information to our Partners, your personal information is subject to their privacy policy. We have no liability or responsibility for these privacy policies or the use of any Personally Identifiable Information transferred to Partners.

If you no longer wish to be contacted by our partners you must contact that partner directly to opt-out. We may use third-party tools or services to provide you with certain services or programs. Our Partners change from time to time, and therefore it is not possible to provide an exhaustive list. We strive to select trustworthy Partners who offer high quality products or services of interest to you. We encourage you to read these companies' privacy policies prior to using any tool or service which they provide if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you are unhappy with one of our Partners, tell us by e-mailing us at privacy@mysearchresults.com you can write to Attn: Customer Care, Search Results, LLC, 2751 Hennepin Ave S #252, Minneapolis, MN 55405.

We may make third party applications or tools available for download by you from or through the Website. The privacy policies of the third party provider(s) of such applications will apply to your use of such applications.

Search Results may use a third party service providers for the purpose of distributing emails to its registered users and/or toolbar/apps publishers or for providing Search Results with operational services or data and server maintenance/optimization services. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other applicable confidentiality and security measures. Search Results does not share any collected personally identifiable information with any third party other than in the way mentioned in this clause.

Search Results may, by itself, or use a third party service provider to, manage and operate a discussion board or other open forum within the Website for general matters of interest or special program. The use of any "public" area or feature of the Website is subject to the "public" area or feature Terms of Use. Users of the "public" area or feature may choose to place personally identifiable information on messages they post. If you use a "public" area or feature on this Website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these "public" areas or features, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these "public" areas or features.

Search Results may engage in business relations with third party companies and offer unique services to clients of such companies within a private label environment. For such purposes, some pages of the Website may be branded with both the Search Results brand and the third party brand. The third party cannot use the private label environment to collect any personally identifiable information and is prohibited from doing so. This Privacy Policy shall apply to all of the pages in the private label environment.

If you entered the Website by clicking an affiliated link or promotion on another Website, or if you used a site that provides universal registration services to sign up for Search Results services, we will store the ID of that affiliate site in our database along with your computer's User ID. We do this to ensure that the affiliate site receives proper credit for any subsequent toolbar or app you may build using our platform.

Search Results reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

### Security of Personal Information

Search Results is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee that the information you provide to us is completely safe, although we are careful to try to prevent problems. There may be technical problems beyond our control that may make it accessible to unauthorized persons.

When sensitive personal information such as a credit card number is transmitted over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption via the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Credit card numbers are NOT stored on our servers, but are only transferred to the payment processor using a secure connection during the actual purchase. After your purchase we do NOT have your credit card number anymore.

### Third Party Web Sites

The Search Results web sites may contain links to third-party web sites over which we have no control or responsibility regarding content, privacy policies, or practices. By accessing the Website and downloading the Search Bar, you hereby grant Us permission to display promotional information, advertisements, and offers for third-party products, offers or services (collectively “Advertisements”) from Our advertising partners (collectively “Partners”). The Advertisements may include, without limitation, content, offers for products or services, data, links, articles, graphic or video messages, text, software, music, sound, graphics or other materials or services. The timing, frequency, placement and extent of the Advertisements changes are determined in Our sole discretion. We suggest that you review the privacy policy applicable to any third party site that you visit. This privacy policy applies only to our own web site at www.mysearchresults.com. Please note that all on-line and telephone credit card orders for Search Results products may be processed by a third party.

### Web Site Security

Our web site utilizes industry standard security technology to protect the security, integrity, and privacy of Personal Identifying Information from unauthorized third-party access. The Personal Identifying Information resides behind a firewall with access restricted to authorized Search Results employees and their agents.

### Changes to the Search Results Privacy Policy

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will update this to this Privacy Policy, and post these changes on the Website or other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email to privacy@mysearchresults.com or write to us at:

**Search Results, LLC**  
**Attn: Legal Department, Privacy Policy Issues**  
**2751 Hennepin Ave S, Suite 252**  
**Minneapolis, MN 55408**

Last updated: January 2014

This Search Bar Privacy Policy (Policy) describes how we treat personally identifiable information when you download and use the Default Tab search bar (Search Bar) created by Search Results for the website and/or a client publisher (Publisher) working with Search Results. Search Results will notify you if we materially change this Policy, at which time you will have the opportunity to discontinue using the Search Bar and Portal. This Policy is also subject to our general privacy policy statement for the Search Results website, located at www.Search Results.com/privacy. If you have questions or concerns regarding this Policy, please contact us at by email at info@mysearchresults.com.

### Collection, Use and Disclosure of General Statistical Information and Automatically Collected Information

When you visit our web site we gather certain general information, such as frequency of downloads, number of hits on our web site, and usage statistics with respect to our software products. This information is referred to throughout this policy as "General Statistical Information". We use and store this data only on a collective basis, in summary form, rather than on an individual basis. This data helps us to determine how and the extent to which certain parts of our web site and software are used. The stored General Statistical Information does not contain any Personal Identifying Information about you or any of our other users.

When you open an HTML email message from us or install a third party application offered by us during installation of recommended software, we automatically record certain data using technology, including cookies (defined below) and IP addresses. Such data include the email message you opened and the third party application you installed. This information is referred to throughout this policy as "Automatically Collected Information." We store this data on an individual basis but it is used only in summary form. This data helps us evaluate the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. The stored Automatically Collected Information does not contain any Personal Identifying Information about you or any of our users.

### Personal Information We Collect

We may collect personal information at various times when you use our Services. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. Your participation is voluntary and you have the choice not to disclose any information that we request.

_Installation_ – During installation, we will present you with Offers. You may choose not to accept our Offers. Your participation is voluntary, you are not required to disclose to our Partners any information they request. However, if you provide your Personally Identifiable Information in response to any Offer, we will share it with our Partners so they can provide you with the Offers in which you have expressed interest.

_Contacts/IP Information_ – If you voluntarily submit information or contact us (e.g. password request, technical support), we may keep a record of this communication. We do not merge this information with your Personally Identifiable Information.

_Contact Us_ – We collect your name and email address on the Sites' "Contact us" forms. We use this information for the sole purpose of responding to your inquiry.

_Customer Support_ – If you use the customer support section on the Sites we will collect your email address, topic and any addition information you provide us. We use this information for the sole purpose of responding to your inquiry.

_Affiliate Sign Up_ – If you choose to sign up as an affiliate we will collect your name, company name, URL, mailing address, phone number and email address. Once we receive your application you will receive an email acknowledgement and instructions on how to pay to become an affiliate. We will not use your email address for any other purpose.

### Aggregate Information We Collect

When you use our Services, we may collect tracking information such as your IP address, browser type, the type of operating system you use, details about your computer hardware, the applications you have installed on your PC, the domain name of your Internet service provider, and pages you visited on our Sites. None of the information identifies you personally and we do not link aggregate information to Personally Identifiable Information.

_Cookies_ – A cookie is a small text file sent to your browser. Cookies are stored on your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. We and our Partners use session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once you close your browser, the cookie will terminate. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's help file.

We use cookies to: 1) Remind us of who you are and to access your account information (stored on our computers). We also use cookies to store your zip code and other information you have submitted for other services, such as displaying your local weather; 2) Record your Blog URL and Username on your local computer to allow us to remember you on your next visit; 3) Estimate our audience size. Each browser accessing our Services is given a unique cookie which is then used to determine the extent of repeat usage, usage by registered users and unregistered users, and to help target advertisements based on user interests; 4) Allows our Partners to track visits to their sites and stores. This information collected by cookies is sometimes called "clickstream" or "click trail" and may also describe which pages you have seen; 5) Measure certain traffic patterns, for example which of our Sites you have visited. We use this information to understand our users' habits so that we can make each new experience on a Site a better one. We may also use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you will see. We do not store Personally Identifiable Information in our cookies and we do not tie the information in our cookies to our customers' Personally Identifiable Information.

Some of the Partner Offers on our Services may also use cookies. We have no control over our partners' privacy policies. We also have no control over their cookies, the information collected and its use.

_Web beacons or Pixels_ – We and our Partners employ a software technology that helps us better manage content on our site. Web beacons or Pixels are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. They track your online Web movement. We embed Pixels invisibly on Web pages. They are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by Pixels to our customers' Personally Identifiable Information. Some of the Partner Offers may also use Pixels. We have no control over our partners' Pixels. We also have no control over how they use information collected.

### Disclosure of Personal Identifying Information

Partners may sponsor Offers or we may co-sponsor an Offer with a Partner through the software. You should always assume data collected when you fill-in an Offer will be shared with a Partner. If an Offer requires you to leave our websites, you should know that our Partners may collect Personally Identifiable Information about you. We do not control these Partner sites. This Privacy Policy does not cover our partners' websites and information practices. Once you have voluntarily submitted information to our Partners, your personal information is subject to their privacy policy. We have no liability or responsibility for these privacy policies or the use of any Personally Identifiable Information transferred to Partners.

If you no longer wish to be contacted by our partners you must contact that partner directly to opt-out. We may use third-party tools or services to provide you with certain services or programs. Our Partners change from time to time, and therefore it is not possible to provide an exhaustive list. We strive to select trustworthy Partners who offer high quality products or services of interest to you. We encourage you to read these companies' privacy policies prior to using any tool or service which they provide if you should have any concerns about how they will care for your personal information. If you are unhappy with one of our Partners, tell us by e-mailing us at privacy@mysearchresults.com you can write to Attn: Customer Care, Search Results, LLC, 2751 Hennepin Ave S #252, Minneapolis, MN 55405.

We may make third party applications or tools available for download by you from or through the Website. The privacy policies of the third party provider(s) of such applications will apply to your use of such applications.

Search Results may use a third party service providers for the purpose of distributing emails to its registered users and/or toolbar/apps publishers or for providing Search Results with operational services or data and server maintenance/optimization services. We require that these parties agree to process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other applicable confidentiality and security measures. Search Results does not share any collected personally identifiable information with any third party other than in the way mentioned in this clause.

Search Results may, by itself, or use a third party service provider to, manage and operate a discussion board or other open forum within the Website for general matters of interest or special program. The use of any "public" area or feature of the Website is subject to the "public" area or feature Terms of Use. Users of the "public" area or feature may choose to place personally identifiable information on messages they post. If you use a "public" area or feature on this Website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these "public" areas or features, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these "public" areas or features.

Search Results may engage in business relations with third party companies and offer unique services to clients of such companies within a private label environment. For such purposes, some pages of the Website may be branded with both the Search Results brand and the third party brand. The third party cannot use the private label environment to collect any personally identifiable information and is prohibited from doing so. This Privacy Policy shall apply to all of the pages in the private label environment.

If you entered the Website by clicking an affiliated link or promotion on another Website, or if you used a site that provides universal registration services to sign up for Search Results services, we will store the ID of that affiliate site in our database along with your computer's User ID. We do this to ensure that the affiliate site receives proper credit for any subsequent toolbar or app you may build using our platform.

Search Results reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

### Security of Personal Information

Search Results is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. However, we cannot guarantee that the information you provide to us is completely safe, although we are careful to try to prevent problems. There may be technical problems beyond our control that may make it accessible to unauthorized persons.

When sensitive personal information such as a credit card number is transmitted over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption via the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Credit card numbers are NOT stored on our servers, but are only transferred to the payment processor using a secure connection during the actual purchase. After your purchase we do NOT have your credit card number anymore.

### Third Party Web Sites

The Search Results web sites may contain links to third-party web sites over which we have no control or responsibility regarding content, privacy policies, or practices. By accessing the Website and downloading the Search Bar, you hereby grant Us permission to display promotional information, advertisements, and offers for third-party products, offers or services (collectively “Advertisements”) from Our advertising partners (collectively “Partners”). The Advertisements may include, without limitation, content, offers for products or services, data, links, articles, graphic or video messages, text, software, music, sound, graphics or other materials or services. The timing, frequency, placement and extent of the Advertisements changes are determined in Our sole discretion. We suggest that you review the privacy policy applicable to any third party site that you visit. This privacy policy applies only to our own web site at www.mysearchresults.com. Please note that all on-line and telephone credit card orders for Search Results products may be processed by a third party.

### Web Site Security

Our web site utilizes industry standard security technology to protect the security, integrity, and privacy of Personal Identifying Information from unauthorized third-party access. The Personal Identifying Information resides behind a firewall with access restricted to authorized Search Results employees and their agents.

### Changes to the Search Results Privacy Policy

If we decide to change this Privacy Policy, we will update this to this Privacy Policy, and post these changes on the Website or other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us by email to privacy@mysearchresults.com or write to us at:

**Search Results, LLC**  
**Attn: Legal Department, Privacy Policy Issues**  
**2751 Hennepin Ave S, Suite 252**  
**Minneapolis, MN 55408**

Last updated: January 2014
